## **GUNAWAN**

+62895364618671 | gugun050500@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/gunawan-ilahgun/ | https://github.com/ilahgun | portfolio: ilahgun.me | Kabupaten Bogor, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a Full-stack Web Developer who graduated from Informatics Engineering from Nurul Fikri Integrated Technology College. I have experience working on projects through Independent Study in the Merdeka Campus program, projects in lectures, and collaborative projects. As an adaptive learner, I have successfully overcome various problem-solving challenges individually and as part of a team. Therefore, I am ready to continue to grow and contribute to the programming field with passion and dedication.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

PT. Kinema Systrans Multimedia | ((Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Agu 2023 - Des 2023)

Full-stack Web Developer

- · Design website pages using Figma
- Implement design and create website using ReactJS Vite.
- · Design databases and build APIs using NodeJS and Express.js.
- Set up and deploying website using Virtual Machine from Google Cloud Platform.
- · Project collaboration using Github.

### PT. Nurul Fikri Cipta Inovasi | ((Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Agu 2022 - Des 2022)

Full-stack Web Developer

- · Project collaboration using Github.
- · Layouting template website content.
- · Implement design and build APIs using Larave.
- Deploy and hosting website that have been finished into Webmin.

## Koperasi Karyawan Indocement | (Field Work Practice during Vocational High School)

(Sep 2016 - Okt 2016)

IT Support

- · Installasi Software and Operating System
- Troubleshooting Hardware & PC Components.
- · Network Setting

### **EDUCATION**

#### Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Terpadu Nurul Fikri - Depok, Indonesia

(2020 - 2024)

Bachelor in Information Engineering (GPA 3.92 / 4.00)

SMK Budiniah - Bogor, Indonesia

(2015 - 2018)

Computer and Network Engineering

## **SKILLS**

Hard Skills: HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript. PHP, Python, MySQL/MariaDB

Soft Skills: Team Work, Communication Skills, Problem Solving and Time Management

Software Skill:

- Framework & Library: ReactJS Vite, Express.js, Laravel, Codeigniter, Tailwind & Bootstrap.
- Tools: VSCode, GitHub, Figma, Trello, Postman, MySQL Workbench.

# **FEATURED PROJECT**

- Go Paper A website developed to manage paper waste.
- Khairul Ummah Information website for the Khairul Ummah Orphanage Foundation located in Bogor district.
- Movie Database A movie recommendation website that takes API keys from the TMDB database.
- · Covid A world covid information website.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Web Development Infinite Learning (MSIB Batch 5), 02 January 2024
- Full-stack Web Developer NF Computer (MSIB Batch 3), 31 December 2022